[
//2nd grade Science
{
  question: "What do you call a skinny booger?",
  correct: "Slim Pickins.",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What’s the difference between boogers and broccoli?",
  correct: "Kids don’t eat broccoli.",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What smells the best at dinner?",
  correct: "Your nose!",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Did you pick your nose?",
  correct: "No, I was born with it!",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "If you were a booger….",
  correct: "I’d pick you first",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What do you find inside a clean nose?",
  correct: "Fingerprints!",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Why can’t your nose be 12 inches long?",
  correct: "Because then it’d be a foot!",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What did one eye say to the other eye?",
  correct: "Don’t look now, but something between us smells.",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Why don’t snowmen eat carrot cake?",
  correct: "They’re afraid it has boogers in it!",
  incorrect: [],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Which is largest?",
  correct: "The Sun",
  incorrect: [“A happy kitten”, “A jumping puppy”, “The slimy worm”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Which weighs more?",
  correct: "Five pounds of rocks",
  incorrect: ["One pound of feathers"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "There are two of these on my nose. I breathe and smell through them.",
  correct: "Nostrils",
  incorrect: [“Eyelashes”, “Lips”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "You are listening to music. Which sense are you using?",
  correct: "Hearing",
  incorrect: [“Smelling”, “Touching”, “Tasting”, “Seeing”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Our body has how many sense?",
  correct: "5",
  incorrect: [“3”, “4”, “5”, ”99”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "You can see germs with your eyes.",
  correct: "False",
  incorrect: [“True”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "All germs are bad.",
  correct: "False",
  incorrect: [“True”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "You should always use soap and water to wash your hands.",
  correct: "True",
  incorrect: [“False”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Germs help keep your body healthy.",
  correct: "True",
  incorrect: [“False”],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Why does your body digest food?",
  correct: "For energy",
  incorrect: ["For sleep", "For watching TV", "For your hair"],
  difficulty: 1
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Did you know? Unless food is mixed with saliva, you can’t taste it.",
  correct: "Yes",
  incorrect: ["No"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Did you know? Human thigh bones are stronger than concrete.",
  correct: "Yes",
  incorrect: ["No"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Did you know? Your tongue is the fastest healing part of your body.",
  correct: "Yes",
  incorrect: ["No"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Did you know? 8% of people have an extra rib.",
  correct: "Yes",
  incorrect: ["No"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Did you know? Your most active muscles are in your eyes.",
  correct: "Yes",
  incorrect: ["No"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "The main purpose of boogers is:",
  correct: "To keep bad things out of your body.",
  incorrect: ["To be gross!", "To make you sweat.", "To answer these questions!"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Science"
},


//3rd Grade science
{
  question: "During which stage does a caterpillar become a chrysalis?",
  correct: "Pupa",
  incorrect: ["Egg", "Larva", "Adult"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "An organism with no eyes, no legs, no mouth, and and wings might be a:",
  correct: "Plant",
  incorrect: ["Worm", "Snake", "Butterfly"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},

{
  question: " Humans breath in oxygen, what gas do they breath out? ",
  correct: "B. CO2",
  incorrect: ["A. Oxygen.","C. Helium.", "D. HO2SO4."],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What is a scientist who studies the body called?",
  correct: "Physiologist",
  incorrect: ["Veterinarian", "Biologist", "Meteorologist"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What is connected to your bones to help them move?",
  correct: "Muscles",
  incorrect: ["Brain", "Blood", "Other Bones"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What provides information to your brain about external conditions?",
  correct: "Nerve Receptors",
  incorrect: ["Heart", "Bones", "Blood Vessels"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What is the scientific or medical name for the skull?",
  correct: "The Cranium",
  incorrect: ["The Femur", "The Gluteus Maximus", "Humerus"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Science"
},




//2nd grade math
{
  question: "9 - 7 = ?",
  correct: "2",
  incorrect: ["1", "3", "16"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "20 - 5 = ?",
  correct: "15",
  incorrect: ["0", "4", "5"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "8 - 3 = ?",
  correct: "5",
  incorrect: ["2", "3", "4"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "12 - 4 = ?",
  correct: "8",
  incorrect: ["4", "6", "16"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "4 - 0 = ?",
  correct: "4",
  incorrect: ["2", "0", "8"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "9 - 9 = ?",
  correct: "0",
  incorrect: ["9", "18", "20"],
  difficulty: 1,
  subject: "Math"
},


//3rd grade Math
{
  question: "Which addition problem is the same as 525+379?",
  correct: "500 + 300 + 20 + 70 + 5 + 9",
  incorrect: ["50 + 30 + 20 + 70 + 50 + 90", "500 + 300 + 20 + 90 + 5 + 7", "250 + 250 + 300 + 30 + 60 + 20"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "Which addition problem is the same as 45 + 917?",
  correct: "9 hundreds + 4 tens + 1 ten + 5 ones + 7 ones",
  incorrect: ["7 hundreds + 9 tens + 5 tens + 1 ten + 7 ones", "9 hundreds + 4 hundreds + 1 ten + 5 tens + 7 ones", "9 hundreds + 5 tens + 1 ten + 4 ones + 7 ones"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "Which expression could be used to find the value of 871 + 140?",
  correct: "8 hundreds + 1 hundred + 7 tens + 4 tens + 1 one",
  incorrect: ["8 hundreds + 1 hundred + 7 tens + 4 ones + 1 one", "8 ones + 1 one + 7 ones + 4 ones + 1 one", "8 tens + 1 hundred + 7 ones + 4 tens + 1 one"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "93 + 45 is the same as:",
  correct: "90 + 47",
  incorrect: ["80 + 35", "85 + 33", "95 + 23"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "Which addition problem is the same as 350 + 473?",
  correct: "50 + 300 + 400 + 30 + 40 + 3",
  incorrect: ["30 + 50 + 40 + 70 + 40 + 3", "300 + 70 + 400 + 500 + 40 + 3", "70 + 30 + 50 + 300 + 40 + 3"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "Which addition problem is the same as 23 + 501?",
  correct: "5 hundreds + 2 tens + 3 ones + 1 one",
  incorrect: ["2 hundreds + 5 tens + 3 ones + 1 one", "2 tens + 5 ones + 3 hundreds + 1 one", "1 hundred + 5 ones + 2 tens + 1 one"]
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "What is the product of 2 and 70?",
  correct: "140",
  incorrect: ["72", "104", "270"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "Sanders ran for 22 minutes. Gabe ran 7 minutes longer than Sanders did. Helen ran 12 minutes less than Gabe. For how many minutes did Helen run?",
  correct: "17 minutes",
  incorrect: ["3 minutes", "27 minutes", "41 minutes"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "What is 342 - 184?",
  correct: "158",
  incorrect: ["162", "242", "268"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "Fill in the blank: 56 + __ = 7",
  correct: "8 days",
  incorrect: ["27 days", "49 days", "63 days"],
  difficulty: 2,
  subject: "Math"
},

// 4th Grade Math
{
  question: "128 / 8",,
  correct: "16",
  incorrect: ["17", "24", "8"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "60 * 5",
  correct: "120",
  incorrect: ["-120", "130", "90"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "81 / 3 ",
  correct: "27",
  incorrect: ["9", "13", "20"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "100 * 10",
  correct: "1000",
  incorrect: ["100", "-100", "10000"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "90 / 30",
  correct: "3",
  incorrect: ["4", "8", "12"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "225 / -15",
  correct: "-15",
  incorrect: ["15", "-16", "17"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},
{
  question: "400 / -20",
  correct: "20",
  incorrect: [ "-20", "21", "-12"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Math"
},

//4th Grade Science
{
  question: "What term best describes an electrical charge formed on the outside of an object?",
  correct: "Static Electricity",
  incorrect: ["Insulation", "Conduction", "Magnetic Field"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Which property of light breaks white light into the separate colors of the rainbow?",
  correct: "Refraction",
  incorrect: ["Reflection", "Light Waves", "Absorption"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Which circuit had two or more paths for a current to flow through?",
  correct: "Parallel Circuit",
  incorrect: ["Battery Circuit", "Series Circuit", "Magnetic Circuit"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What materials are attracted to magnets?",
  correct: "Iron",
  incorrect: ["Copper", "Aluminum", "Wood"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "How much blood is in the average human body? ",
  correct: "A. About 10 pints. ",
  incorrect: ["B. About 2 pints.","C. 21 pints.","D. No pints, who needs pints?"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},

{
  question: "What is the hollow space in the middle of a bone filled with?",
  correct: "Marrow",
  incorrect: ["Air", "blood", "solid bone"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What is the human body's largest organ?",
  correct: "Skin",
  incorrect: ["Heart", "Lungs", "Stomach"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Which body system moves blood throughout the body?",
  correct: "Circulatory",
  incorrect: ["Nervous", "Digestive", "Skeletal"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What strong flexible tissue holds bones to other bones to support the joints?",
  correct: "Ligaments",
  incorrect: ["Tendons", "Spine", "Muscles"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "Which of the following joints provide the widest range of movement?",
  correct: "Ball and socket",
  incorrect: ["Hinge", "Gliding", "Immovable"],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},
{
  question: "What helps the red blood cells carry oxygen through out the body?",
  correct: "C. Hemoglobin.",
  incorrect: ["A. Bubbles","B. Globetrotters.", "D. Chloroplast. "],
  difficulty: 3,
  subject: "Science"
},



]